

Muhammad Amir

Fahmy

- **+6013-7746263**
- amir12102009@gmail.com
- Melaka Tengah, Melaka, Malaysia
- khunamir.github.io/portfolio-2.0



PROFILE



My name is Muhammad Amir Fahmy. I am a 23 years old fresh graduate with a Bachelor of Information Systems (Hons.) Intelligent Systems Engineering. I have a deep interest in Data Science and Natural Language Processing. I am certified Data Science Professional by IBM and also a certified Power BI Data Analyst Associate by Microsoft. I love to read, finish courses and finding new things to learn. I am looking to apply all my industrial and academic knowledge in a related position and continue to expand my knowledge in an industrial environment.

EXPERIENCE



Mar 2023 - Aug 2023

Software & Automation Apprentice

KPMG Malaysia (Lighthouse)

Petaling Jaya, Selangor

- Develop new website for internal client using Django regarding Malaysian Business Reporting System (MBRS)
- Experienced meeting with clients
- Conduct UAT testing
- In charge of reviewers module

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020

IT Intern

Merpati Blue

Batu Berendam, Melaka

- Assist in proposal creation for new website projects
- Update products information in client's e-commerce website
- Experience web consultation communication with clients
- Assists in setting up Personal Computers for a new client's office

EDUCATION



May 2021 - Aug 2023

Bachelor of Information System (Hons.)

Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM)

Shah Alam, Selangor

- Intelligent Sytems Engineering
- Published a paper on IEEE through the 2022 3rd International Conference on Artificial Intelligence and Data Science (AiDAS)
- Participated in a programming competition (Mini Pro-solve)
- Dean's List Award for semesters 3, 4, 5 and 6 (CGPA)
- Quarter-finalist for Inter-faculty Sports, Quarter-finalist for Lions League, Champion for Inter-program Sports (Badminton)

Sep 2018 - Mar 2021

Diploma in Computer Science

Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM)

Jasin. Melaka

- Graduated with Vice Chancellor's Award (CGPA 3.81)
- President of UiTM Jasin Cycling Club

PROJECTS



- Sports Diet Fuzzy Based Expert System (React Native, Django)
- Badminton Hobbyist Fee Payment Web Application (React)
- Topic Modeling of Science and Technology News (Natural Language Processing)

CERTIFICATIONS



- IBM Data Science Professional
- Microsoft Certified: Power BI Data Analyst Associate
- Certified Data Analyst Associate (Asia Pacific University of Technology and Innovation)
- Certified Entry-level Python Programmer (Python Institute)